多数"和什么押韵来着? 没有
What rhymes with majority? Nothing.
不是吧 你还在写那首关于新议长的搞笑歌么?
Come on, you still working on that funny song about the new Speaker?
算了吧 哦 优先
- Give it a break. - Oh, priority.
权威 姐妹会
And authority. Sorority.
哦 天哪 那个韵可以找到成千上万的词
Oh, my God, there's a million words that rhyme with it.
哦 不 不 不 不!啊 !
Oh, no. No, no, no! Gah!
看Jonah是从哪过来的
Look where Jonah's coming from.
哦 那个笑容 那串钥匙 哦 天哪
Oh, that grin, the keys. Oh, God.
给了他西翼主管级停车位
He's been given West Exec parking.
嗯 停车位的终极目标
Yeah, the holy grail of parking.
早上好 先生们 多么令人愉快的一天
Good morning, gentlemen. What a delightful day.
我本来打算走去上班 但之后...
I was gonna walk to work, but then...
你拿到了西翼主管级? 那只是个停车位 Dan
- You got West Exec? - It's just a parking spot, Dan.
要嫉妒的话 你得成为某种浅薄的...
To be jealous of that, you'd have to be a shallow kind of...
我不知道 二逼 我猜
I don't know, dick, I guess.
女士 这是在人质任务期间的情报室
This is the situation room, ma'am, during the hostage mission.
我们需要批准一张可公开的照片 好的
We need to approve a photo for release. - Okay.
瞧瞧
Let's see.
哦 天哪 瞧Ben
Oh, my God. Look at Ben.
看他咖啡杯的大小
Look at the size of his coffee mug.
呀 你可以在那里面藏个婴儿了
Jeez, you could hide a baby in that thing.
哦 但我看起来很不错 哼?
Ooh, I look nice, though, huh?
是的 你是
Yeah, you do.
你看起来忧心忡忡而坚毅
You look concerned, but steely.
没错 就像个女兵
Yeah. - Like a lady soldier.
哦 到时不会有任何老兵出席
Oh, there are not gonna be any veterans
明天的青少年祷告早餐吧?
at this teen prayer breakfast thing tomorrow, are there?
没有 女士 没有缺胳膊断腿的人
No, ma'am. No missing legs.
好吧 这是你要见的年轻领袖们的所有资料
Okay, here's all the details of the youth leaders
哦 该死的
- that you're gonna be meeting. - Oh, man.
谁会这么年轻就虔诚于宗教信仰啊?
Who the hell is religious as a teenager?
我就是
I was.
我的意思是 为了基督 抽点大麻吧 对不?
I mean, smoke some weed, for Christ's sake, right?
哦 上帝 看总统
Oh, God, look at the president.
呀 他看起来太... 他看起来有双下巴
- Jeez, he looks so... - He looks jowly.
啊 看他的脸颊
Ah, look at those cheeks.
就像他脸上挂了两个女士小手包一样
It's like two little clutch bags attached to his face.
上帝呀 包包 你总是想着包包
Oh, my God, with the bags. It's always bags with you.
你得跳出包包的地盘
Got to get out of the bag zone.
来啊 Gary
Come on, Gary.
先生 先生们
Sir. - Gentlemen.
你计划的新人口统计学研究让我感到很激动
Very excited about this new demographics study you're planning.
你本就该如此 统计梦会揭示选举战场
You should be. Dream Metric will reveal
还原它的本来面貌
the electoral battleground as it truly is.
它和显微镜的发明一样伟大
It's comparable to the invention of the microscope.
我能向你说说我在策略方面的想法吗
Would it be okay if I showed you some ideas I have regarding strategy?
没有时间 Egan先生
No time, Mr. Egan.
大部分都是动画的 但我把它们放到视频网站上了
They're mostly Flash based, but I put them on YouTube.
我刚说了我没时间
I just said I had no time.
截止时间不饶人啊 对吗 Mike
We're all being hit by deadlines, right, Mike?
是的 先生 它们可以像船帆一样绕圈扇你巴掌
Yes, sir. They can swing around and smack you like a boom.
你玩船 Mike?有只船?
You sail, Mike? Have a boat?
呃 是的 先生 一条87年Gulfstar 50 不错的舱式游艇
- Uh, yes, sir. An '87 Gulfstar 50. - Great cruiser.
没什么特别的 不过她能解决问题
Nothing fancy, but she gets the job done.
就像铸铁锅或者kevin Bacon一样 (万年大配 片极多)
You know, like a cast-iron skillet or Kevin Bacon.
我的是条Lagoon 380
I've got a Lagoon 380.
双体船么? 没错
- Catamaran? - Yeah.
那可是真男人的扬帆之航
That's real man's sailing.
在抢风调向时倾斜身体 你的大蛋蛋就会浸到海水中
Leaning out in the tack, your big man balls dipping in the salty sea.
说得正在点子上 我的朋友
You're right there, my friend, yeah.
我没有孩子也没打算有
I have no children and I wish for none,
但她是我的家人
but she's my family.
你知道 我曾经去伊利湖玩过动力艇
You know, I once went powerboating on Lake Erie.
冲得可过瘾了
Amazing rush.
我得走了
I need to go.
别对我们这群玩帆船的说动力船 Dan
You don't talk powerboating to us sailors, Dan.
有他妈什么不同啊!
What's the fucking difference?
嘿 副总统在?
Hey. Veep in?
不在 Dan 你有空闲干坐在这?
- - No. You have time to just sit there?
你已经将大楼里所有人的秘密都打听清楚了?
You've already bugged the shit out of everyone else in the building?
抱歉 什么?再说一次
I'm sorry, what? Say that again.
Jonah 出去 否则我会试试我防狼喷雾的效果
Jonah, out. Or else I'll see if my pepper spray works.
早 伙计们 早
- Morning, guys. - Morning.
13000 不 是14500
13,000. No, 14,500.
那是你今天对镜自夸的次数吗?
Is this the amount of times you've admired yourself in the mirror today?
不 我只是在猜薪水的差别
No, I'm guessing that's the difference in salary
这个工作和你刚面试过的那个工作的薪水
between this job and the one that you just interviewed for.
你觉得我去面试了?
You think I had a job interview?
我知道你有一个面试
I know you had a job interview.
怎么知道的 大侦探? 简单的妆容 高高的领口
- How, Sherlock? - Simple makeup, higher neckline.
平底鞋和那条裙子不搭 说明你包里大概会有双高跟鞋
Flats don't go with that dress, which means you probably have heels in your bag.
本地面包店的咖啡表明你去过
Coffee from corner bakery implying you were at
第十八街的某个小店
one of the lobbying shops on 18th.
我喜欢这种东西
I love this stuff.
除了这个 还有人打了你的分机
That and somebody called your extension
确保你有正确的地址
to make sure you had the right address.
嘿 Danny Chung今晚会表演么
Hey, is Danny Chung gonna be performing tonight?
真的吗?他要干什么?
Really? What's he gonna be doing?
我想他会把bon Jovi从燃烧的坦克里拖出来 (摇滚巨星)
I think he'll be pulling Bon Jovi out of a burning tank
唯恐我们忘记他妈的他是个怎样的战争英雄
in case we all forgot what a fucking war hero he is.
没错 不 我们没有官方评论
- Yeah. - No, we have no official comment.
不 那可不是不评论
No, that is not a non-comment.
我们只是没有在评论而已 什么?
- We're just not commenting. - What?
这张照片是怎么流出去的? 什么?
How did this photo get out there? - What?
那我们能把它从网上彻底删除吗?
Can we delete it off the Internet, then?
不 我不知道我在说些什么
No, I don't know what I'm talking about.
什么?这儿发生了什么?
What? What's going on here?
女士 是白宫发布的这张照片
Ma'am, the White House released this picture.
什么? 不 不 这不是...
What? No, no. This isn't...
Amy 这不是我们批准的那张照片
Amy, this isn't the photo that we approved.
不是 看这个
No. - Look at this.
看起来像是一个男人断腿的时候我在玩推特
It looks like I'm tweeting when a guy loses his leg.
是的 的确如此
Yeah, it does, ma'am.
女士 这是Kent干的
This is Kent's doing.
他这是在耍我 我要去宰了他
He's trying to screw me. I'm gonna go stab him.
我去宰了他
I'm stabbing him.
是的 从此刻开始 这是不可... 好的 出去
- Yeah, from this point. It's unprec... - All right, get out.
出去 你也是 Amy
Get out. You, too, Amy.
我不希望有任何目击者在这 我没开玩笑
I don't want any witnesses in here. I'm not kidding.
我去准备化尸酸 是的
- I'll start running the acid bath. - Yeah.
是照片的事么?
This is the photograph?
不 只是想知道你是否觉得这件毛衣和这条裙子相配
No, just wondering if you think this sweater goes with the dress.
瞧 其他的照片里照总统的角度都不对
Look, the other photos caught POTUS at a bad angle.
脸颊太突出 什么?
- Vis-à-vis jowls. - What?
看着不好看 他看上去就那样 那就是他的脸
- It's a bad look. - That's how he looks. That's his face.
你为什么不干脆拿张我照得好的 然后把我P进去?
Why didn't you just take the good one of me, Photoshop it in?
我没法虚构历史 女士 我不是约瑟夫·斯大林
I can't airbrush history, ma'am. I'm not Joseph Stalin.
不 确实 你不是他
No, that's true. You're not.
你连他十分之一的魅力都没有
You don't have a tenth of his charm.
好吧 我还是继续去弄我的Jim Marwood的歌吧
Okay, I'm just gonna go work on my Jim Marwood song.
啊 我们正在预算对话中 就差一点达成一致了
Uh, we're in budget talks, reaching across the aisle.
总统不希望议长先生被嘲笑
POTUS does not want the Speaker mocked.
哦 那么现在我需要Dan  Mike
Oh, so now I have to have Dan and Mike,
Rodgers还有Hammershit 一个下午的时间去弄首新歌出来?
Rodgers and Hammershit, come up with a new song in an afternoon?
我们可以自嘲
We can laugh at ourselves.
或许你该拿这张照片开玩笑
Maybe you should do a funny bit about the photograph.
控制局面 控制这个吧
Own the situation. - Own this.
她当时正一心几用 你需要挂上电话
She was multitasking. - You need to get off the phone.
那是女人可以做到的事情 就像保持身体清香还有包装礼物那些
It's a thing women can do, like smelling nice and wrapping gifts.
好吧 再见 Tom
- Okay. - Bye, Tom.
这事你处理好了么?
Were you on top of this or what?
我们忙着将年青人里流行的东西
We were busy writing youth culture references
写进那首关于议长的搞笑歌曲
in a funny song about the Speaker.
我甚至不知道你刚说的是什么
I don't even know what you just said.
你笑什么 逼脸绿巨人?
What are you laughing about, Jolly Green Jizzface?
我 我...抱歉 女士 真该死 还有你为什么会在这?
- I was... sorry, ma'am. - God damn, why are you even here?
哦 我过来是告诉您 您现在是模因了 女士 (meme: 自私的基因一书中提出的文化传播因子)
Oh, I came here to tell you that you're a meme, ma'am.
我是模因 女士? 你在说什么? 说英文 孩子
I'm a meme ma'am? What are you talking about? Speak English, boy.
模因 是一种网络现象
A meme, an Internet phenomenon.
好吧 是的 这张照片被处理过的版本
Okay, yes. There are Photoshopped versions of this
在推特上到处转发
springing up all over Twitter.
您在《独立宣言》的发表日... 哦 天哪
- You at the Declaration of Independence... - Oh, my God.
和抹大拉的马利亚在耶稣罹难日（圣经故事）
With Mary Magdalene at the crucifixion,
还有04年的海啸
the 2004 tsunami.
如果有海啸 你本来就会看手机 因为你要查天气预报
If there was a tsunami, you'd be genuinely looking at your phone
你知道吗 我不需要你说话
'cause you'd be checking the weather.
我们怎样才能停止这狗屎的模因女士?
You know what? I don't need you to talk.
不 只有模因 女士 不是模因女士
How do we stop this meme ma'am shit?
通常48小时后它们就销声匿迹了
No, it's just a meme, ma'am. Not a meme ma'am.
但有时它们会爆发然后变成超级模因
And usually they flame out after about 48 hours,
就像Downfall (二战影片 其希特勒片段被广为恶搞)
but sometimes they blow up and become a super meme
或者江南Style
like Downfall or Gangnam.
我喜欢江南 我刚说了什么?
- I love Gangnam. - What did I just say?
如果把它放到Reddit或者Tumblr就有可能会 (前者为社交新闻网 后者为最大轻博客网站)
If it gets on Reddit or Tumblr, that can happen.
是的 好吧 你得从这里出去 可以吗?
Yeah, okay. You've got to get out of here, okay?
带走所有的这些无意义的音节 出去
Take all these meaningless syllables with you and just get out.
是的 一点没错 女士 哦 今晚的晚宴见
Yes, absolutely, ma'am. Oh, and I will see you at the dinner tonight.
哦 天哪 啊
Oh, my God, yeah.
好吧 嗯 这是一堆破烂里面唯一的好事了
Okay, yeah, that's a cherry on top of this whole turd cake.
噢 你的腿 你能放...?
Ooh, your leg. Could you put...?
把你的腿摆好让我看到它的全貌
Fix your leg so I can see your whole leg.
放好 哦 好吧
Fix it. Yeah. Okay.
总统说我们不能在Vic Allen晚宴上
POTUS said that we can't do the song about the Speaker
唱那首关于议长的歌 我们不能唱
at the Vic Allen dinner. We can't do it.
议长之歌被砍掉了? 没错
the Speaker song is cut? - Yeah.
那很好笑的 没那么好笑
it was hilarious. - it was not that hilarious.
你疯了吧 哥们 那会让人们尿裤子的
You're out of your head, dude. That would have made people piss in their pants.
Hey, hey, hey!
让我们作首关于Kent的歌吧
Let's do a new song about Kent.
Kent? 嗯
- Kent? - Mm-hmm.
你觉得? 拿我们自己开玩笑 这是他说的
- You think? - Make fun of ourselves, that's what he said.
我喜欢这个主意
I kind of like that.
的确 我挺喜欢这个
I do, I kind of like that.
好吧 我们写吧 我没有问题 就这么干吧
All right, we'll do it. I have no problem with that. Let's go.
那就是我们要做的 干吧
That's what we're gonna do. Let's go.
停止这种扰乱议事的行为 捣蛋的家伙
Just stop the filibuster, buster.
不错  但不押韵
- That's good. - That's not a rhyme.
你只是用了同样的词来造词而已
You're just matching a word with the same word.
写下来 Dan 我正在状态中
Just write it down, Dan. I'm in a zone.
搞笑歌曲是人渣的标志
Comedy songs are the mark of a douchebag.
你错了 你知道为什么吗?
You're wrong. You know why?
三个词...搞怪 Al Yankovic (美国歌曲恶搞专家)
Three words... Weird Al Yankovic.
狗屎的Al Yankovic
Shit Al Yankoshit.
闭上你的嘴 成吗?
You shut your mouth, okay?
请...保护那些濒危的鹅 Bruce
Just... protect the endangered goose, Bruce.
这很棒 模仿《离开爱人的五十种方法》的恶搞之作 (副歌部分有很多以姓名和行为押韵的歌词)
These are all great. A parody song of 50 Ways to Leave Your Lover.
好主意 真的?
Great idea. - Really?
没错 如果第一个就失败
- Yeah. - If the first one bombs,
人们就会坐在那想去他妈的
people are gonna be sitting out there thinking,
还有49个这样的玩意
Shit the bed, we got 49 more of these to go.
帮帮石油厅吧 Bobby   这个不错
Help the oil lobby, Bobby. That's a good one.
咱们跟踪Jonah吧
Let's follow Jonah.
这太幼稚了
That is so childish.
我们为什么做这个?
Why are we doing this?
因为它毫无意义 就像我们做的其他事一样
Because it's pointless, like everything else that we do.
你仍然恼怒着 因为你没法巴结上Kent?
You still pissed you can't get in with Kent?
没人可以 他一半是机器人 一半是机器人
Nobody can. He's half robot, half robot.
他是机器人 是的 那就是挑战 Mike
- He's a robot. - Yeah, that's the challenge, Mike.
瞧 大学里所有的女孩都喜欢我
See, in college all the girls liked me.
唯一一个女孩 聪明 对我没兴趣
There was this one girl, smart, who had no interest in me.
她也不是同性恋 我确认过了
She wasn't gay either. I checked.
所以搞上她就成为了我的使命
So it became my mission to sleep with her.
那么你得手了?
And did you?
没有
No.
那个失败的阴影一直缠住我直到今天
And that failure has haunted me to this very day.
我有个类似的故事 不过恰好相反
I have a similar story, but the other way around.
大学里只有一个女孩对我感兴趣
In college there was only one girl that was interested in me.
结果她是个女同性恋
And it turns out she was actually a lesbian.
每个人都有些不在状态
Everyone is a little off.
Dan很郁闷 Sue正在找另一份工作
Dan is bored. Sue is looking for another job.
什么?真的?
What? Really?
唔 然后你对Gary说的话...
Mmm, and the stuff you're saying to Gary...
什么? Gary对我生气了?
What? Gary's not happy with me?
什么?
What?
因为就算我对他的脸开一枪他都会很高兴
Because he'd be happy if I shot him in the face.
他会的 我真的想过这事
He would be. I've actually thought about it.
他觉得自从他有了那个女朋友Dana
He feels since he got that girlfriend Dana,
你对他就很奇怪
you've been weird with him.
好吧 可以麻烦你...你能不能不...
Okay, can you please... can you please not...
看吧 这个就是另外一点 腿的事
See? That is another thing. The leg.
好吧 他的确失去了一整条腿
Well, he did lose a whole leg.
那就像他该有的一半 对吗?
That's like half of what he should have, right?
我很好 瞧 我能搞定这个事
I'm fine. Look, I can handle this whole thing.
我能 Sue
I can. Sue.
你对这里极其重要
You are incredibly valued here and I was wondering
我在想我们能做什么事来留住你
if there's anything we could do to make you want to stay with us.
更多的钱 女士 我能搞定 欢迎回来
- More money, ma'am. - I'm on it. Welcome back.
为您服务是我的荣幸
Honored to serve.
刚用一美元把Sue买下来 谁是下一个?
Just bought Sue for a dollar. Who's next?
Gary 我会和他聊聊
- Gary. - I'll talk to Gary.
在办公室外谈怎么样?
How about doing that outside of the office?
邀请他一起晚餐 或许
Invite him to dinner maybe.
喔 我从未和Gary一起吃过饭
Wow. I've never eaten with Gary before.
我有在他旁边吃过饭 但...
I've eaten next to him, but...
好吧 哦 这个我可以
Okay, yeah. I can do that.
早上好 Jon蛋蛋 你真可悲
- Good morning, Jonad. - You're pathetic.
Jon睾睾!
Jonuts!
是的 等你有办公室再朝我冲过来 嗯?
Yeah, come at me when you guys get an office, huh?
每个人都讨厌他 没错 但我们是最先讨厌他的
- Everyone hates him. - Yeah, but we hated him first.
哦 没错 在讨厌他变成流行之前很久我们就讨厌他了
Oh, yeah, we hated him long before it was even fashionable to hate him.
这就像野生动物纪录片
This is like a wildlife documentary.
Jonah在他的自然栖息地 他可能在树丛后拉屎
Jonah in his natural habitat. He might defecate in a bush.
这是什么 我不知道
- What is this? - I don't know.
Jonah 嘿
Jonah. - Hey.
忙着呢? 没有
Busy? - No.
我只是需要来拿一些这种长尾夹
I just had to get some of these binder clips.
哦 从另外一幢大楼 嗯?
- Oh. - From another building, huh?
是的 白宫已经没有了
Yeah, we ran out at the White House.
但是 难道那里没有一个人能帮你弄到一些?
Isn't there a guy, though, that can get that for you?
哦 你可能认为会有一个
Yeah, you'd think there would be.
是的 但他...因为生病而休息了
Yeah, but he's... he's off sick.
是谁? Steve
Who is? - Steve.
可怜的老Steve怎么了?
What's poor old Steve come down with?
他有糖尿病 哦 喔 那是个大病
- He has diabetes. - Oh, wow. That's a big one.
哪一型? 2型
What type? - Two.
哦 2型的症状是什么来着?
Yeah. What are the symptoms of two again?
哦 他就是感觉不大舒服
Oh, he's just feeling bad.
他...你知道的 他血糖太高
He's... you know, he's sugary.
是的 或者他血糖不够
- Yeah. - Or he's not sugary enough.
没错 哦
Right. - Yeah.
还有其他的症状吗
Are there any other symptoms?
哦 他的手腕肥大 你知道吧
Yeah, he's got fat wrists. You know?
没错 你被Kent赶出来了?
Yeah. You getting freezed out by Kent?
我们一直盯着你 Jonah
We've been watching you, Jonah.
你被废弃了
You're obsolete.
你就像一台旧的录像机 但是嘴更多
You're like an old VCR, but with a bigger mouth.
你们一直跟着我? 没错
You guys have been following me? - Yeah.
你们就像少女侦探 还有她那条嗅屁股的狗一样跟着我
You've been following me like Nancy Drew and his butt-sniffing dog
而无所事事的人是我?
and I'm the one that has nothing to do?
冷静下来 老兄 我们很忙
Cool the honey, bro. We're very busy.
我们正在写一首搞笑歌 闭嘴 Mike
- We're writing a comical song. - Shut up, Mike.
好吧 我也许很闲 先生们
Well, I might have nothing to do, gentlemen,
但至少当我正为此哭泣时
but at least when I'm crying about it,
我是在我在车里哭
I am crying about it in my car
停在西翼高级停车场
in West Wing Exec parking.
赢下Denver有50种方法
50 ways to win in Denver
La-lum.
嘿 女士 再次感谢您的晚餐邀请
Hey, ma'am, thanks again for inviting me to dinner.
没问题 这是我的荣幸
- Sure. - It's an honor.
事实上我将它写在了日记里并整整凝视了它五分钟
I actually wrote it in my diary and stared at it for a full five minutes.
这是我对你的款待...
My treat for you...
我们刚准备好一切
Would you set it all up, please
还有菜单请过目...
And check the menu, too?
当然
Of course.
不不不 我是说真的
No, no, no, I actually really do mean that
请搞定餐厅和其它事情
Figure out the restaurant and everything.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
唔 你...   什么 Gary?
- Um, do you... -   Yes, Gary?
什么事?
What is it?
Dana能一起来吗?
Can Dana come along?
哦 真的吗 不是
- Oh, really? - No.
那是个糟糕的主意
That was a bad idea.
如果她不能去也没关系
It's okay if she can't.
唔 不 那挺好 行
Um, no, it's good. Fine.
你会喜欢她的
You are gonna love her.
她是个真女人 哦 我等不及了
- She's a total gal's gal. - Oh, I can't wait.
她说这个... 你能帮我拿一下咽喉喷剂吗
She says this one thing... - Can You get me my throat spray?
我需要那个 你带了吗 当然
I need that. Do You have it? - Sure.
Mi fa so la ti do.
不不不 不要和我对歌
No, no, no, don't sing it with me
那会弄疯我
That fucks me up.
Jim 副总统女士
Jim. - Madam Vice President.
我总是觉得我应该行屈膝礼
I always feel like I should curtsy,
然后才想起来那不对劲
and then I remember that doesn't make sense.
不 那确实不对劲
No, it certainly does not.
你知道Amy Brookheimer 我的幕僚长
You know Amy Brookheimer, my chief of staff.
议长先生 真高兴再次见到你
Mr. Speaker. It's nice to see you again.
Amy 现在是我变老了还是你变年轻了?
Amy. Now, am I getting older or are you getting younger?
我们都老了
We're both getting older.
那是第三种选择 当然 那是好东西
That's the third option, of course. That's great stuff.
我知道今晚不开玩笑了
I understand there's gonna be a bit of a joke truce tonight.
敌对的短暂停止
A cessation of hostilities.
完全正确 我今天不会说任何笑话
Absolutely. There will be no jokes from me.
我不会提那张照片
I'm not going to mention the photograph.
你当时是在网购吗?
Were you Internet shopping?
我开玩笑的
I'm joking.
又或者我没有 好了
Or rather, I'm not. There we are.
好吧
Okay.
你知道的 我出席过同样的祷告早餐
You know, I was at that same prayer breakfast
在一个月前 哦 是吗?
- about a month or so ago. - Oh, were you?
他们不是很棒的孩子吗 他们是很棒
- Aren't they great kids? - They're great.
而且作为年轻选民他们看上去很激动
And they seemed excited as young voters
为一个老兵成为总统的可能性而激动
about the possibility of a veteran becoming president.
不见得是我 好吧
not necessarily me. - Okay.
哦 他们看起来为女人成为总统的可能而兴奋
Well, they seemed very excited about the possibility of a woman becoming president.
不见得是你
Not necessarily you.
哦 我在外交政策上的更大影响能满足我的需要
Well, my enhanced foreign policy role will serve me well.
嘿 成为国际关系的头很不错
Hey, it is good to be on top of international relations.
当然 那么机会就少了
Sure. - so there are fewer opportunities
像我这样的人要冒生命危险的机会
for guys like me to risk our lives.
哦 完全正确 一点没错 嗯
Oh, absolutely. Absolutely, yeah.
还有肢体 唔嗯
And limbs. - Uh-huh.
你不打算吃完这个么? 我要了 好了
Are you not finishing this? I'm gonna take it. Okay.
Amy 你该停止暴饮暴食
Amy, you should stop eating so much.
他妈的你在说什么
What the fuck are you talking about?
你在压力性进食
You're stress eating.
我没有 我在吃甜点
I'm not. I'm having dessert.
我认为你让办公室的压力一直影响着你
I think you're letting the pressures of the office get to you.
你几乎没有办公室以外的生活 你不去健身房
You barely have a life outside. You don't go to the gym.
你不去看电影 你几乎不呆在家里
You don't go to the movies. You're barely at home.
那是事实
That's true.
我是说 我希望我没有猫
I mean, I hope I don't have a cat
因为 相信我 那可怜的混蛋死了
because, believe me, that poor fucker's dead.
你需要去约会 Amy
You need to date, Amy.
为自己找一个会洗澡的政治狂热份子
Find yourself a political nerd who also showers.
我只是为你好
I'm just saying I'm looking out for you.
我不希望你变成一个肥胖的 神经质的怪人
I wouldn't want you to become a fat, neurotic freak.
这是身为朋友的忠告
Speaking as a friend.
今晚我们有很多特别的节目
We have a lot of special performances tonight
还会有很多乐趣 Danny Chung
- and a lot of fun ahead. - Danny Chung.
他把一个男人从坦克里拖了出来
So he pulled a guy from a tank.
而你救出了四个被俘的男人
You saved four guys from captivity.
嗯 顺说 他们没有被烧伤
Yeah, and they weren't burnt, by the way.
Chung的人有张像圣诞火腿的脸
Chung's guy had a face like a Christmas ham.
Danny Chung州长!
Governor Danny Chung!
谢谢
Thank you.
好的 谢谢
All right, thank you.
你知道的 这次的组织者遭遇了很多挑战
You know, this administration has faced many challenges.
但直到现在也没有人
But until now, nobody's thrown down
做B-box的口技表演
a beatbox challenge.
那一点也不吸引人
That isn't impressive at all.
他只是在吐口水 对吧 没错
- He's just spitting, right? - Yeah.
女女女...女士们先生们
L-l-ladies and gentlemen,
明明明...明尼苏达在此
M-m-m-m-minnesota's in the house.
我说 哦 钱还是性?
I said, Well, was it money or sex?
然后他说 不 福克斯新闻的那个人
And he said, No, the guy from Fox News
是唯一停下来并问路的
is the only one who stopped and asked for directions.
谢谢
Thank you.
认真一下 就一会
To be serious for just a moment,
我认为我们需要送给
I think we need to give a big round of applause
副总统一次隆重的掌声
to the vice president for the part that she played
为她在解放这群被非法囚禁
in setting free those young guys
的年轻人事件里所做的贡献
who had been held against their will for so long.
副总统女士 谢谢
Madam Vice President, thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
当然 她做的所有事就是打开她卧室的门
Of course, all she had to do was unlock her bedroom door,
但同样感谢你
but thanks anyway.
哦 至少她没有俯视他们
Well, at least she didn't look down her nose at 'em.
你知道的 当他们在找这个东西的时候
You know, when they're looking for the thing.
你知道 但谢谢 好吧 好吧
You know, but thank you. Okay. Okay.
非常感谢您听我说话
Thank you so much for listening to me.
我需要个笑话 我需要个笑话 谢谢 晚安
- I need a joke. I need a joke. - Thank you. Good night.
谢谢
Thank you.
Jim Marwood 女士们先生们
Jim Marwood, ladies and gentlemen.
让我们为他放弃这个吧
Let's give it up for him.
伙伴? 肉
Mate? - Meat.
肉? 不 静音 静音
- Meat? - No, mute. Mute.
静音 这
Mute. Here.
Jim Marwood 我们该怎么对你?
Jim Marwood, what are we gonna do with you?
我会告诉你 那是一个我希望能静音的音箱(议长)
I'll tell you, that's one speaker I'd like to put on mute.
好吧 哦 我也来一个
Okay, well, I'm gonna give this a shot.
你只需要记住我不是Selina Dion (席琳迪翁梗)
You just need to keep in mind that I'm not Selina Dion.
好吧 哦 你知道吗
Okay, well, you know what?
开始吧 男孩们
Let's hit it, boys.
问题全部都在你的脑袋里
The problem is all inside your head
Kent如此对我说
Kent said to me
你要是用上逻辑 答案很简单
The answer is easy if you take it logically
要是你分析选举 它叫选举学
If you analyze elections, it's called psephology
Kent说了 50种方法来赢下丹佛
Kent says there's 50 ways to win in Denver...
Kent说有50种方法
Kent says there's 50 ways
来赢下丹佛
To win in Denver
你刚说你会削减赋税 Max
You just say you'll cut tax, Max
别装成菁英 Pete
Don't be elite, Pete
亲亲胖宝宝 Abie
Kiss a fat baby, Abie
解放你自己
Set yourself free
别摆欧洲范儿 Ian
Don't be European, Ian
说去他的法兰西 Lance
Say screw France, Lance
也许是德国佬 Hernman
Maybe the Germans, Herman
荷兰人 瑞典人
The Dutch, the Swedes
资助辆巴士 Gus
Subsidize a bus, Gus
别支持人流 Joyce
Don't be pro-choice, Joyce
少玩点女人 Rex
Not too much sex, Rex
听我的话吧
Take it from me
做个饼状图 Art
Make a pie chart, Art
分析分析资料 Max
Analyze the facts, Max
别生活在宫殿里 Alice...
Don't live in a palace, Alice...
这太蠢了
This is imbecilic.
你是对的 蠢透了
You're right. It's asinine.
不 保持微笑 Ryan先生
No, keep smiling, Mr. Ryan.
我假笑 你也得这么做
I'm smiling falsely. So should you.
不要提起以色列 Catherine
Don't mention Israel, Catherine.
早上好!
Good morning!
你应该灌张唱片
You should cut an album.
哦 你能想象吗? 你镇住了全场啊
- - Oh, can you imagine? You killed it.
你比Chung干得好
You killed better than Chung killed
事实上他被干掉了
and he's actually killed.
我得向Kent假装我不喜欢
I had to pretend not to like it to Kent
而且在他假装喜欢的时候假装喜欢
while pretending to like it like he was pretending to like it,
但实际上他不喜欢而我非常喜欢
but he didn't actually like it and I actually really liked it.
哦 你好 先生
Oh, hello, sir.
女士 你昨晚的歌让我的嘴唇弯曲
Ma'am, your song last night made my lips curl.
唔...朝上弯的
Uh... - Upwards.
能帮我个小忙么?
I have a small favor to ask.
好的 当然 我能为你做什么
Okay, sure. What can I do you for?
哦 我的统计梦人口调查项目已经差不多可以开始了
Well, my Dream Metric demographic program is about to launch
我想从你组里借一个人 两周
and I would like to borrow a member of your team for two weeks.
哦 你想要Dan?
Oh, you want Dan?
不 我要Mike
No, I want Mike.
唔 不 你不想要我 先生 你确实想要Dan
Uh, no, you don't want me, sir. You do want Dan.
他很棒 我马上就会有个大回弹
- He's great. - I've got a big bounce coming on.
我能感觉到 我和你一样
I can feel it. I'm like you.
不 唔唔 你不能带走Mike
No, uh-uh, you can't take Mike.
他是我的传媒主管
He's my director of communications.
你在开玩笑?你不能带走他
Are you kidding me? You can't have him.
总统的欧洲访问 赫尔辛基协议...
POTUS's European visit, the Helsinki agreement...
哦? 他没法去了
Yeah? - He Can No longer Make it.
债务上限谈话马上就要崩了
Debt ceiling talks are on the verge of collapse,
所以他需要有人代他去
so he needs someone to go in his place.
现在要么是国务卿要么...
Now either that's the Secretary of State or...
Mike 再三考虑后
Mike, on second thought,
我认为这整个梦...
I think that this whole Dream...
统计 统计
Metric. - Metric.
统计梦什么的听起来似乎不错
Dream Metric thing sounds kind of fantastic.
你不这样认为吗 是的 女士
- Don't you think? - Yes, ma'am.
总统下达的命令 那么...
Comes from POTUS, so...
十五分钟后底下大堂见 Mike
I'll see you down the hallway in 15 minutes, Mike.
我会给你说 情况的
I'll pipe you aboard.
女士 祝您欧洲旅途愉快
Ma'am, enjoy your trip to Europe.
谢谢
Thank you.
Jonah也会加入此次行程
Jonah will be making the trip as well.
唔 等等 你在说什么
Uh, wait. What are you talking about?
你要把我的传媒主管带走
You're taking my director of communications
然后给我Jonah?
and you're giving me Jonah?
这是总统的指示
This comes from POTUS.
女士 女士 请不要让他带走我
Ma'am. Ma'am, please don't let him take me.
我不要去数字营
I don't want to go to numbers camp.
我帮不了你 走吧 求你 求你
- I can't help you. Just let go. - Please. Please.
放开我 行吗?
Let go of me, all right?
很明显你给Kent留下了好印象
Obviously you made an impression on Kent.
我不留印象的 女士
I don't make impressions, ma'am.
我真的有过室友坚持我不存在的经历
I've literally lived with people who insist I was never there.
你不做任何媒体简介 明白吗
You give no press briefings. Understood?
我会是Mike 你会是丑陋的我
I become Mike, you become an ugly me.
酷 我可以搞定新媒体
Cool. I'll handle new media.
女士 我会给您带来大量的线上曝光率
Ma'am, I'm gonna get you major online traction.
Reddit  Tumblr 没问题
Reddit, Tumblr, boom.
什么都行 只要你别用我在空军二号上的卫生间
Whatever. Just don't use my bathroom on Air Force Two.
那有另外一个卫生间吗? 欧洲
- There's another bathroom? - Europe!
哦 我的天哪(法语) 没错 我知道 那会非常有意思
- Oh, mon dieu. - Yeah, I know. It's gonna be fun.
真的 真的很有趣 那会很有趣
- Really, really fun. - It'll be really fun.
现在 我很抱歉 但我不认为 我们能和Dana一起吃晚餐了
Now, I'm so sorry, but I don't think we're gonna be able to do the dinner with Dana.
哦 我们可以提前到午餐 就那么办
Oh, we can bring it forward to lunch. Let's do that.
哦 唔... 嗯?嗯?
Oh. Uh... - Yeah? Yeah?
哦 是的 好吧 嗯? 嗯? 好吧
Oh. Yeah. Okay. - Yeah? Yeah? Okay.
那么就说我要做进口佩科里诺干酪的生意的事
So cut to I'd set up a business importing pecorino cheese.
你知道那个牌子的的奶酪吗
Are you familiar with that brand of cheese?
唔 我认为... 它和巴马干酪很像 但还是不同
- Uh, I think... - It's like parmesan, but it's different.
它们非常不一样 你用来形容...的词是?
- They're very different. - What's the word that you use to describe...
微黑 微黑
a duskiness. - a duskiness.
那不是很棒吗? 你会用微黑来形容过奶酪吗?
Isn't that great? Would you ever describe a cheese as dusky?
打死也不会 没有 我不会那么做
Not in a million years, no. I wouldn't do that.
但是...那么你进口巴马干酪?
But so... so you import parmesan?
佩科里诺 抱歉 佩科里诺
- Pecorino. - I'm sorry, the pecorino.
直接从意大利托斯卡纳进口
They're direct from Tuscany,
也就是说它们途经佛罗伦萨
so that means it comes in through Florence.
如果我用了西西里的供应商的话--事实上我不会
If I were to use a Sicilian supplier, which I wouldn't,
我的运营费用就会加倍
my overheads would double.
他们就会给她一个
And they would have made her an offer
她无法拒绝的价格
that she couldn't refuse.
实际上 黑手党极少插手奶制品业
Actually, the mafia involvement in the dairy industry is minimal.
你是对的 我很抱歉 我不该这么多嘴
You're right. I'm sorry, I didn't mean to be flippant.
想想吧 在《教父》里 没有奶酪
Think about it. In The Godfather, no cheese.
是 你说的对 你知道我是对的
- Yeah, you're right. - You know I'm right.
砰! 那是她的标语
- Boom! - That's her catchphrase.
她抓到你了 你得小心
She got you. You got to be so careful.
好吧
Okay.
那么 Gary 嗯?
- So, Gary. - Yeah?
这次午餐是让我来表达对你重视
This lunch is about me saying that I value you.
我无法告诉你 听到你那么说我们真是太高兴了
I cannot tell you, we are so happy to hear you say that...
如果你可以... 啊哼
If You could just... - Ahem.
我想说谢谢
And I want to say thank you
为你替我所做的一切
for all that you do for me.
啊 那太好了
Aw, that's so nice.
我为你准备了个小礼物
And I got you a little gift.
不! 是的 我有
- No! - Yes, I did.
哦 那太好了
Oh, that's so nice.
看这个 新的leviathan包包 (澳大利亚品牌)
Look at this. A new Leviathan.
一个...新的leviathan包!
A Lev... a new Leviathan!
那不是很棒吗
Isn't that great?
它的设计是不是一样的 亲爱的?
Does it have the same layout, honey?
因为让你去熟悉另一个那会花很长的时间
Because it took you so long to learn the other one.
不 这很好 我可以学一个新的设计 没问题
No, it's fine. I can learn a new layout. It's fine.
你想要一个不一样的?
Do you wish that I had gotten you a different kind?
没有 没有 没有 没有 我很喜欢
No, no, no, no. I love it.
我喜欢我的新包!
I love my new bag!
我可以缝一些新口袋进去 没问题
I can just sew some new pockets in. That's okay.
因为这是个象征 没错
- 'Cause it's a symbol. - Yeah.
这是给你的 唔唔
- It's for you. - Mm-hmm.
找我的?
Is that for me?
哦 没错 找你的 是Amy
Oh, yeah. That's for you. It's Amy.
嘿 你好吗
Hey, what's up?
Kent之歌突然带来了些负面的注意
The Kent song has suddenly gotten some negative traction.
对欧洲的引用... 我开了免提
- References to Europe... - I'm putting you on speaker.
由副总统Selina Meyer演唱的劣作中对欧洲的引用
References to Europe in an ill-conceived song
引起了愤怒
performed by VP Selina Meyer have sparked outrage
此大陆上部分国家 问题在哪?
- in parts of the continent. - What's the problem?
歌词别来欧洲范儿 Ian
The lyrics don't be European, Ian,
说去他的法兰西 Lance...那个部分
say screw France, Lance... that whole bit.
我正将那些需要注意的链接发到你的iPad上
I'm sending the alert links to your iPad.
抱歉 Gary 我能用下我的iPad吗
Excuse me, Gary. Can I have my iPad?
你带了吗 哦 这里
- Do you have that? - Oh, right here.
给你 抱歉 谢谢
Here You go. Sorry. - Thanks.
你知道 当你还在思考的时候
You know, while you're getting to know your own mind,
我就了解了你想法
I'm getting to know the rest of you.
而且妈妈喜欢
And Mama likes.
抱歉 妈妈喜欢那个
Excuse me. - Mama Like it.
我很抱歉 对不起 Gary 就一会
I'm so sorry. Excuse me, Gary, just for a second.
我不知道我的密码是什么 你知道...?
I don't know what my password is. Do you know what it...?
这是4G 你不需要无线网络 女士 但标志都在这
- It's 4G. You don't need a Wi-Fi, ma'am. - But the signals are all here.
你需要做的就是关掉无线网络
You know what you got to do is shut the Wi-Fi off.
那就会迫使它转向4G 你知道我是对的
That forces it into 4G. You know I'm right.
好吧 别那么做 我不确定怎么做
- Okay, let's not do that. - I'm not sure how to do that.
不 不 不 那是机密的 我不会碰任何东西
- No, no, no. That's confidential. - I won't touch anything.
我不会碰任何东西 啊 我刚开始了一场和伊朗的战争
I won't touch anything. Oops, I just started a war with Iran.
玩笑 它一点都不好笑
- Joke. - That's not even remotely funny.
那只是我的经典笑话之一
That's just one of my classic jokes.
枪乌贼和西葫芦? 哦 那是给这位Gary的
- Calamari and zucchini? - Oh, that would be for Gary here.
好的 给 也许来点橄榄?
- Okay, here you go. - And maybe some olives?
哦 别 别 别 别 出去
- Oh, no, no, no, no! - Get out!
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
好吧 我们的欧洲访问
Well, our European visit
刚刚变成通往地狱的单向旅程然后回来
just got turned into a one-way trip to hell and back.
事实上那是个回程 你知道吗
- That's actually a return. - You know what?
就两秒钟 你能不能闭上嘴
Could you just shut it just for like two seconds?
我们为什么不走? 没错 我们得提前结束这次午餐了
- Why don't we go? - Yeah, we've got to cut this lunch short.
但是 你知道 你会永久持有你的包 所以管他妈的
But, you know, you're gonna have your bag forever, so what the fuck?
下午好 先生们
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
统计梦在此刻开始
Dream Metric begins at this second.
今天就是始发点 Mike
Today is ground zero. Mike.
没错
Right.
这就是美国指数
This is the index to America.
它会让我们了解人们将如何投票
It will let us know how people will vote
甚至在他们自己意识到之前
before they even know themselves.
这个项目颠覆了
This program revolutionizes the way we think
我们关于自己是如何思考的想法 Mike
about the way we think. Mike.
真兴奋
It's exciting.
一个小时前 德国总理
Within the last hour, the German chancellor
表达了他对这种评论的失望
expressed his disappointment at the remarks.
他以为他是哪根葱?
Who the hell does he think he is?
《世界报》（法国报纸）的乔治 · 丹尼斯
'George Dennis' of 'Le Monde'
称副总统是一典型的美国土包子
called the vice president a typical American hick.
我认为发音是Georges Denis呢
I think it's pronounced Georges Denis.
我不是土包子 去你的 德帕尔迪厄 (法国影星 大鼻子情圣)
I'm not a hick. Screw you, Depardieu.
我认为那上了Reddit和Tumblr
I think it just got on Reddit and Tumblr
然后就从那上面爆发了
and just exploded from there.
唔 那些词听起来极其耳熟
Uh, those words sound mighty familiar.
Jonah?
我只是超喜欢那首歌
I just liked the song so much.
然后我猜你想把它传播出去
And I thought you wanted it out there,
所以我就把它放那了
so I just put it out there.
给我滚下飞机
Get off the plane.
什么?
What?
滚下去 女士 我们正在滑行中
- Get off of the plane. - Ma'am, we're taxiing.
我认真的 你妈的给我滚下去
I don't give a shit. Get the fuck off my plane.
嗯 他妈的给我滚下去
Yeah, get the fuck off of my plane.
我无法相信你居然把那个放到Tumble上面了
I cannot believe that you put that out on Tumble.
不 是Tumblr 好吧
- No, Tumblr. - Okay.
熄火! 我们能让Jonah下去么 麻烦?
- Stop the engines! - Can we get Jonah off the plane, please?
起来!
Get up.
你所有的特权都将被剥夺
All of your privileges are gonna be removed.
好吧 但不包括停车位 没错 停车位
- Okay, but not the parking. - Yeah, the parking.
等等 什么?你有停车位? 现在没有了
- Wait, what? You have parking? - Not anymore.
是的 现在没了 但我甚至还没有买车
- Yeah, not anymore. - But I didn't even own a car.
我刚签了一辆日产Cube 两年的租约
I just had to sign a two-year lease for the Nissan Cube.
让他下去 好吧 伙计们 我的包在行李架上
- Get him off. - Okay, guys, my bag is in the hold.
他有个大包包吗? Gary
Does He have a big bag? - Gary.
好了 好多了?
Okay. - Better?
都好了 全好了
- It's all good. - It's all good.
我很好 十分好
- I'm fine. - Totally fine.
很好
Great.
这次航程有多久?
How long is this flight?
数字 它们从不结束 对么?
Numbers, they never end, do they?
但那就是它们的优点...
But that's what's good about them...
它们会一直继续下去
they keep going.
喔
Aw.
他应该被自杀监控
He should really be on suicide watch.
没错 确保他挺过去
Yeah, make sure he goes through with it.
那是拉丁裔选票 对吧?
That's the Latino vote, right?
那个?
That thing?
Mike 来我办公室 是 先生
- Mike, my office. - Yes, sir.
笔
Pen.
我几天前从你这租了一辆日产Cube
I leased a Nissan Cube from you the other day.
如果我不再需要它 我有哪些选择?
What are my options if I don't need it anymore?
我能把它退回去么
Can I just give that back?
不行?
No?
纸
Paper.
帮帮石油厅 Bobby
Help the oil lobby, Bobby
别搞疯华尔街 Pete
Don't piss off Wall Street, Pete
不要提起以色列 Catherine
Don't mention Israel, Catherine...
滚出特区
Get out of DC
Steve.
耶!
Yeah!